<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Follow up Reminder(s) email alert for all Severity Levels – Recipient: FUO; Trigger: Case is Open AND survey Response date +5 business days, then every 2 days for 3 months – All Severity Levels</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Reminder 2 E-mail to FUO</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>REMINDER - ACTION ALERT – Survey Response Received – {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Oracle_Project_Number__c} – {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Project_Profile_Project_Name__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear Colleague:

You are receiving this reminder because the status of a follow-up action assigned to you is still set as &apos;Open&apos; or &apos;In Progress&apos; and has not been closed since the survey response was received from the client contact. This action is now overdue. Please address the action required as described below immediately.

<<<<<<< HEAD
A client contact has responded to a survey invitation associated with a project that is in your jurisdiction. The response has been assigned a Severity Level {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Severity_Level__c} - {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Severity_Type__c} based on the Client Contact’s response to three questions associated with Likelihood to Recommend, Health &amp; Safety and Request for Contact. For more about Severity Level definitions click here.
=======
A client contact has responded to a survey invitation associated with a project that is in your jurisdiction. The response has been assigned to a {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Severity_Level__c} - {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Severity_Type__c} case based on the Client Contact’s response to three questions associated with Likelihood to Recommend, Health &amp; Safety and Request for Contact. For more about Severity Level definitions click here.
>>>>>>> INT

Key Response Information:

Date Client Survey Response Received  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Survey_Received_Date__c}
Project Number  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Oracle_Project_Number__c}
Project Name  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Project_Profile_Project_Name__c}
Likelihood to Recommend Rating  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Likelihood_to_Recommend__c}
Health &amp; Safety Rating  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Satisfaction_Health_Safety__c}
Request for Contact Response  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Request_for_Contact__c}
Full Survey Response  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Customer_Survey_Response__c}
Severity Level  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Severity_Level__c}
Survey Respondent  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Survey_Contact__c}
Company Name  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Oracle_Client_Name__c}
Survey Respondent Phone Number  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Survey_Contact_Phone__c}
Survey Respondent Email Address  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Survey_Contact_Email__c}
Project Manager Name  {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Oracle_Project_Manager__c}



Action Required:

A case has been opened in Salesforce for follow-up actions associated with this response to be documented. As the follow-up action owner, you are responsible for getting in touch with the client contact, identified above as the survey respondent, in person or via phone within 5 business days.

Follow the steps below:

•	Review requirements for follow-up action with the client contact which depend on the assigned Severity Level. Click here for more information on addressing follow-up actions.

•	Before you reach out to the client contact, consider contacting the Project Manager, {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Oracle_Project_Manager__c}, to get any needed background information.

•	For survey responses where the Likelihood to Recommend Rating is 6 or less, consider contacting the Regional Quality Manager, {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Regional_Quality_Manager__c} and Regional Risk Manager, {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Regional_Risk_Manager__c} (and the ECAM/CAM Account Executive, if applicable) to discuss as applicable and appropriate.

•      Transfer any notes or comments from this conversation with the client contact to the case and close the case to prevent future reminders. If further analysis or corrective action is necessary, please document accordingly in the case. Click here for more information on documenting follow-up actions and closing a case.

This action has been escalated to {!CFM_Survey_Case__c.Escalation_Owner_EO__c}, the Escalation Owner. Timely follow-up when a client survey response is received is a key factor in the client’s perception of AECOM as a professional, client-focused organization.

Please contact Client Care (ClientCare@aecom.com), if you have any questions about this alert. Click here for more information on the Client Care Program.

Regards,

The Client Care Team</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
