<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Norwich Office - Newsletter - August 2014</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>AECOM Norwich // See further go further</subject>
    <textOnly>AUGUST 2014

Understanding our local market

What are the opportunities, challenges and trends facing our industry here in East Anglia? These are some of the questions we have been posing to local contractors in our recent market survey and we are getting some interesting responses. We will be analysing the results and sharing this with our clients and industry colleagues in the coming months at a series of events.

Contact: Tim Boucher on +44 (0)1603 953003 or +44 (0)7767 770774


Putting Norwich on the map

Newly appointed Minister for Life Sciences and Mid Norfolk MP, George Freeman, was in Norwich earlier this month to open the new Centrum Building at the Norwich Research Park. Our teams provided cost management and CDM-C services on this fascinating building which includes a virtual technology centre and a molecular farming facility. We&apos;re delighted to have played our part in helping the Biotechnology and Biological Sciences Research Council move Norwich another step closer to becoming a world-class hub for research and development.

Contact Holly Davis on +44 (0)1603 953012 or +44 (0)7795 668 960


A healthy order book

We are pleased to formally announce a number of recent project wins for the AECOM Norwich office. These include the Centre for Food Health for the Institute of Food Research and Biotechnology and Biological Sciences Research Council (BBSRC ); Wherry Road Residential; supporting the Freebridge Housing Association; Campbells Meadow Retail Park; the Kings Lynn Innovation Centre; Waltham Forest College Phase 4; Boardman House for Norwich University of the Arts NUCA  and projects with Aviva and the University of East Anglia (UEA).


Top of the class

It was smiles all round on APC(Assessment of Professional Competence) results day with the news that three members of our team, Alex Williamson, Holly Davis and Daniel Hughes, had successfully passed and fully qualified as members of the Royal Institution of Chartered Surveyors (RICS).  All three were helped along the way by our award-winning graduate development programme. Here in Norwich, we have a long history of supporting young people entering the industry by offering strong career development, training, educational sponsorship and mentoring.

Home grown talent

Meet Jon Nelson, our newest director  and recently-appointed Fellow of the Royal Institution of Chartered Surveyors (FRICS). Jon may well be familiar to you as he has been with the business in Norwich for 17 years, starting as a trainee surveyor in 1997 and rising up through the ranks. His FRICS appointment follows a long period of supporting the RICS, as well as the local RICS Matrics which supports people entering or not long in the surveying profession.

Strengthening our teams

This summer we are welcoming a host of new faces to the Norwich office. We have bolstered our project management team with the addition of Andy Tough, Senior Project Manager,and Charlie Richards, Graduate Project Manager. Geraldine Wesby  has joined our CDM-C  team as a Senior CDM Co-ordinatorand we will soon say hello to two new trainee surveyors, Alice Greengrass and Liam Chappel. We are also delighted to be welcoming back Richard Tyrrell, Associate, and Jack Trutch, Project Surveyor,who have both decided to re-join the AECOM team in the last few months.


Our APC stars (left to right): Holly Davis; Daniel Hughes; and Alex Williamson
Newly-promoted Director, Jon Nelson

AECOM welcomes a host of new faces this summer

Getting active at the
Corporate Games

At AECOM we strive to create an environment where our people can do great work as well as finding time for a bit of fun along the way. With this in mind, a team of seven of us headed down to UEA Sportspark in mid June to take part in the Corporate Games. The day saw us competing in 11 sporting challenges including wheelchair basketball, kayaking and gymnastics and provided a great chance for us to meet people from other local businesses and prove our sporting prowess - we came fifth out of 38! The Corporate Games is part of the Active Norfolk drive to encourage companies to be more active in and out of work.

Supporting SportsAid

We recently hosted the SportsAid Eastern lunch held at the Assembly House, Norwich. Sponsored by local businesses, the event supports local young sportsmen and women who aspire to be our next Olympic, Paralympic and world champions. Bethany Woodward a Paralympic silver and bronze medalist gave an inspiring talk on her career, plans for Glasgow and the road to Rio!


Our team of budding athletes get active at the Corporate Games
AECOM&apos;s Tim Boucher meets Paralympian Bethany Woodward</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
